I've been feeling crazy lately Don't recognize myself
I put my pride on the show Trusting somebody else
But on a summer land falling Don't care what nobody say
The love's gonna win anyway So I'll take the pleasure and pay
I said my stomach but it flies too
You don't know till it might be like that
Then burn it all to the ground
Keeps you up
You're ready?
Yeah
It make me feel like
We're close and nothing the dark can't see the dark
Loads your eyes thinking how much time has it been since I should get off and let it go
I know you're hard and beat so steady
Hey the whole trip let your mind go so we can fly we can fly away
Right tenitas have y'all heard of the movie sing?
Yeah
So do you know Mina the elephant?
That is me
Fun fact it was so much fun being Mina that I wanted to do her song
From the movie is by the legendary Stevie Wonder. Are y'all cool with that?
Let's have some fun y'all. Here we go. Hey.
But some don't know. Don't you worry.
It's so cool.
Wait, let me turn this up a little bit.
We're here.
Are you all so good?
You still with me?
Feeling good. Okay.
Just make just take it man. Just take it man.
So I just put out a new album.
It's called God Must Really Love Me.
And I really, really love all the songs.
this song in particular I just got really vulnerable one day and was just I
was just hit with a wave of anxiety and this world is crazy y'all this world is
really really crazy and so I just put all those feelings into this song and yeah
this is called bird.
What if I pass my prime and I wasted precious time?
What if that well-bronced dry, oh my my, too many anxious nights?
What if you leave like my dad did?
What if I love as days are in past tense?
Feels sick and to me like a magnet,
Wondering what they're gonna say over my casket?
Oh, these what if still in my peace of mind?
If I cough up my hood, me back together
When the world tells me apart, then I remember
You got me in the middle of your hands, and I know
Feels like a weapon, exhale, take a breath in
You take the weight off of my heart
Put me back together, when the world tells me apart
And I remember you got me in the middle of y'all.
This is our last song.
This has been so much fun.
I am so, so blessed to be able to perform with these amazing ladies.
Can you give it up for my band?
One vocals.
Give it up for Jordan on guitar.
We got the pocket queen, on drums.
Lynette.
Lynette on keys, y'all.
Thank you so much.
I'm Tori Kelly.
And yeah, thank you for having me.
This is our last song.
It's called Tokyo.
A quick update before you go, we're doing another Tiny Desk giveaway.
Enter by September 12th, 2026, and you and a friend can win a free trip to D.C. to see
a Tiny Desk concert live in person.
You even get to choose which upcoming show you want to see and it's completely free to enter.
Just go to npr.org slash tiny desk giveaway.
Entering is completely free, but you can get more entries by snagging some
limited edition tiny desk merch or by making a special donation to the NPR network.
Learn more and enter today at npr.org slash tiny desk giveaway.